Based on the number of taps,
it should be coming from this direction.
It's up there!
Something big is headed here...
Is that... a dragon?!
No, it's a wyvern!
It can't be...
Farming Life in Another World
Masshiro hikari no naka me o samashite
hajimatteiku sutoorii
Fumidasu atarashii sekai donna hana o sakaseyou?
Kumori sora datte mizutamari de yogoretatte
Bokura wa susumu
Souzou mo shinai mirai ga matteiru kitto
Deatte deatte tsunagatteku
Waraeba mawari mo egao ni naru
Chiisana tane maite sodateyou
Yagate ookina hana ni naru
Koukai ya shippai wa kate ni shite
Karafuru na shiawase de afureru youni
Bokura te o toriatte wakeatte
I never expected a monster like that
to show up here...
Should I try to drive it away?
No, maybe it'll just ignore us
and pass through here...
Lu, defense!
We need to put out the fires!
This is bad.
Yeah. Should we attack it?
I'm not even sure we can pierce its barrier.
I need to make a decision, and fast.
Should we try to escape into the forest?
No, that won't work.
He can follow us from the sky!
I just need to drive him away... but how?
I can't worry about that now.
I need to do something.
I need to protect everyone!
Is this a spear?
Why?
It doesn't matter. Right now,
I'm going to take this power...
and crush him!
Impossible...
We managed to put out all the fires.
There was some damage to the crop fields,
but all of the buildings are fine.
I see.
It looks like I managed to take it down.
Are there are lot of these creatures?
Well, there are some places where they live...
but running into one of them that's
this large is a very rare occurrence.
Is there any possibility that someone sent
this wyvern here specifically to attack us?
I don't think so.
Even if this wyvern was under
someone's command,
they wouldn't send such a rare and
valuable creature off on its own.
It was most likely
a wild creature acting alone.
I see.
So then, I guess we can safely say
that this was nothing more than
an unfortunate but rare incident.
By the way...
What is it?
Can we eat this thing?
Wyvern meat is said to be a delicacy.
In fact, it's said to be so delicious
that supposedly there was once a king
who sent his army into a den of wyverns
to hunt them and bring them back for
the king to taste and see for himself.
I'm pretty sure that story ended with
them all getting burned to death
and then swallowed whole by the wyverns.
Here's the meat in question.
This is a wyvern round steak,
grilled with spices.
I wrapped the breast meat in leaves
and steamed it.
And for the tail meat, I simmered it
into a stew with vegetables.
I thought it would be really tough,
but this meat is so tender!
And to think, a regular knife
couldn't even pierce its skin.
Thif delicafy if ewy fit as dewifish as if loofs!
I didn't understand any of that.
Mmm... this broth is great.
I faid...
Swallow your food first.
Every bite I take of this tail meat
has more flavor than the last!
Hey, would you have been able
to block an attack
from that spear like
the one he used back there?
Not a chance.
That attack pierced a
3-layer barrier from a wyvern
and then proceeded to
blow right through its chest.
Maybe it was actually a stroke of luck
that Kuro and the dogs were who
we ran into first when we came here.
Yeah, you're right.
What's wrong?
Did I not get all the bones out?
No, it's just... we think we're blessed to
be able to enjoy our meals in good health.
We were just thanking fate
for smiling upon us.
It's not that big of a deal.
This one's delicious, too!
It really is!
Demonic Kingdom of Galgardo
Demon Lord's Castle
You say a wyvern was felled?!
Enough of these jokes!
No, the report we received is true.
Impossible!
One of those simply drawing near requires
that we mobilize our entire military force!
This is...
He was attacked from the ground
and killed in two hits.
One of the demon lord's four great generals
Beezel
Randan
That's absurd!
Enough of these jokes!
One of the demon lord's four great generals
Grattz
It's true.
No way. We can't fight something like that!
And we just finished getting
this year's budget approved!
No...
It's a joke, right?
Stop saying that.
Now then, before fear and panic
begin to spread among our citizens,
it's our job as the four generals
to handle this situation.
I've got it.
Let's resign.
Hey, wait!
Please don't run away from this, Randan!
Gatekeeper Dragons
Dryme's Lair
Did you see that, Gucci?
I saw it with my own eyes.
And what do you think would happen
if I were to receive such an attack?
It would mostly likely
pierce cleanly through you.
What do we do?
It would be foolish to attack.
Yeah, definitely.
The wyvern meat was every bit
as delicious as it was said to be.
But if I'm being honest, there's still
one thing that was missing from the meal.
Ah, are we going to start now?
Is it finally time?
Yeah.
We're making alcohol!
If we're making alcohol out of grapes,
then it's going to be wine.
Apparently, wine exists in this world.
So, everyone was excited to make it
and quickly harvested all the grapes.
Now all that's left is to squash the grapes
and let them ferment.
and to do that, we built...
this!
We're going to walk on top of these?
Yeah. Make sure to stomp them really good.
I'm a little hesitant to stomp on
something that we're going to drink.
If you get tired, you can have
someone switch in for you.
What about you?
I'm in charge of switching
the barrels as they fill up.
By the way, these barrels were
built by the high elf Lalasha
because she knows how to make
containers that are water tight.
Lalasha
Okay!
because she knows how to make
containers that are water tight.
I had her make them right away.
Alright, you guys can start now.
You really sink into them.
Am I doing it right?
Let's see...
Starting moving in a circular motion
around the whole thing.
Okay.
Let's go in this direction.
Yeah.
Careful not to slip and fall.
Okay.
Are you alright?
I-I think so...
I'm sorry that I bumped into you.
Not at all. That was my fault.
You know, I think this would be easier
if we had a way to help keep our rhythm.
One... Two... One... Two...
It might keep all of our movements in sync.
Hm, good point.
I know, we can use that song
we used to sing in our village
while we were all working together.
Ah! That just might work!
A song?
Yes. It goes like this.
One, two, three, go!
Looks like they found their rhythm.
Hey, Lu!
Come on, it's fun!
Okay, then you're coming with me!
Huh? But I'm...
Let's go!
Hey, wait!
Come on!
That was a lot of work.
I'm exhausted, but that was a lot of fun.
Now the yeast on the skin of the grapes
should ferment this for us.
I wonder if we made too much...
16 barrels total
It'll be fine.
I'm sure we'll drink it all right away.
Yeah, I can't wait to drink it.
Don't tell me we didn't make enough...
See? Look how much fun he's having.
So, can't you forgive me
for what I've done already?
Absolutely not!
Goddess of Agriculture
You mistakenly punished
an innocent human's soul,
and sneakily tried to save him,
only to end up sending him to
that horrible Forest of Death!
On top of that, you gave him that spear!
I can't believe you gave him
a replica of the holy lance Gryme!
Well, um... right now he's only
using it as a farming tool.
Plus, I got permission first, remember?
You didn't tell me you were
giving that to a human!
That thing should drain all of their
life force and kill them instantly!
But he's doing fine right now.
I'm sure that he just has
super-fast recovery abilities
because I gave him such a healthy body...
I'm telling you that you were too careless!
And besides that...
And besides that!
Why is the statue that's
supposed to be me an old man?!
Old man
That's not my fault.
I don't want to hear any excuses!
As punishment, you're going to sit there
like that for 300 years, my careless father!
Please forgive me, my daughter!
I'm feeling a strong sense of déjà vu here.
Flora?!
My dear sister!
So, they're actually related somehow.
Yes!
After I heard you were being chased by
that infamous black-hearted angel,
I followed you all the way here.
Who did you say was black-hearted?
Why is she here?!
It was just an expression!
Apparently, Flora is also a vampire.
It's something I used to hear Lu say very often.
Oh, did Lu say that?
And she's related to Lu.
Oh sister, please help me!
Well since you're here, why not relax
and stay with us for a while?
Okay...
I'm having a hard time believing that
this man here is Lu's husband.
Something feels off.
No, never mind!
He's the one who's in charge here,
and he's the master of
all these inferno wolves.
He even took down a wyvern.
I understand now.
I humbly apologize for my rude behavior.
Prostrate
Don't worry about it.
So anyways...
You guys are wolves, Kuro?
I had no idea.
What's the inferno part mean?
Wow! That's amazing!
You've been living with them
this whole time and didn't know?
I believe they're quite well-known
magical beasts...
I guess you can think of this
as sort of an apology
for what Kuro and the wolves
put you through.
We went ahead and prepared dinner for you.
It's great!
This is all fantastic.
What's the soft, white stuff?
Oh, that's called tofu.
After a lot of tries, I finally got it right.
They're made from a type of bean
called soybeans.
Wow, this made from beans?
Flavoring soup with salt is fine and all,
but I really wanted some miso.
Plus, I wanted to be able to put
soy sauce on stuff I eat.
Miso? Soy sauce?
Miso and soy sauce are both made
from fermented soybeans
and are used to add flavor to food.
Fermented?!
Basically...
It seems that in this world,
fermented foods like wine and cheese exist.
However, they aren't aware of the microorganisms
that actually cause fermentation.
I see.
If tiny organisms that we aren't
able to see with our eyes exist,
and if these organisms can cause
transformations in matter without magic,
then that would serve to explain all of this.
Eat or talk. Pick one.
It seems that like Lu, she's also
very passionate about her research.
Eat or talk. Pick one.
It seems that like Lu, she's also
very passionate about her research.
I've found a fascinating new subject
for my research!
I'll be sure to bring the wonders of miso and
soy sauce to all who live in these lands!
And then one day we will all feast upon
miso soup and cold tofu!
After staying here for a few days,
Flora left with great haste and excitement
so that she could make preparations to move.
1 month later
I have returned!
O-okay...
That was really fast.
You even brought the maids with you.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Anne, and I speak on behalf of
the other maids as their representative.
We ask that you put us to use
as you see fit, master.
Uh, you really don't need to be that formal.
By the way, what are those?
They're just normal cows, right?
That's right.
I made sure to pick cows to bring
with me that would give us milk.
This is great.
Now we can make butter and cheese!
Vampires and their clan
A lot
Elves
Wolves
A lot
Spiders
Angels
by myself
= not many
= WEAK
Excuse me!
What? Why are you so close?
I need to leave for a short while.
Sure...
I wonder what she's going off to do.
Meeting
I have returned!
Okay...
I've brought my underlings here as well!
My name is Granmaria.
I'm Kudel.
I'm Corone. It's nice to meet you.
I'm Daga,
the representative of the lizardmen.
And I've prepared this here as well!
It's a chicken!
Does it breathe fire?
It does not.
What about eggs?
It lays them!
I'm glad to hear it.
Thanks to everyone here,
this place just got a lot more civilized.
For the rooms on this side, Lamulias,
I want you to dust them
before we start washing the floors.
Understood.
Ah, sorry for interrupting.
It's fine.
The maids belong to a race of ogres.
I guess it's to be expected
since they're professionals,
but as soon as they showed up
all of our chores got done a lot faster.
However...
The inhabitants of this world don't seem
to cook any complicated dishes.
Frying
Boiling
I tried to teach them all the different
methods of cooking that I knew.
Stir fry
Deep fry
Braising
Dressing salads
Steaming
Heat control
It seems like it got them
interested in cooking all at once.
Dinner is served.
Today I tried making a dish of
killer rabbit with fragrant vegetables.
Wow. So those things
are called killer rabbits, huh?
This looks wild.
They're all very strong,
despite their appearances.
They display both proper manners
and a bit of power.
Then, there are the three angels
that Tia brought with her.
Now then, you're all to patrol
a different region of the forest.
Granmaria, Kudel, and Corone.
I want you to make sure you see everything,
even the tiniest of movements.
Granmaria, Kudel, and Corone.
Understood.
I was wondering why they all showed up
in such serious looking armor.
It turns out that after the wyvern attack,
Tia planned on having them
act as our security on the premises.
I feel safer with them around.
The lizardmen are in charge of all the labor
that requires strength outdoors.
Hey!
The lizardmen are in charge of all the labor
that requires strength outdoors.
Yes, I'll be over in just a moment.
Thanks to them, our construction work
is moving along even faster than before.
By the way, I had their leader Daga
tie a scarf around his arm.
I feel bad, but I'm not able to
tell them apart otherwise.
I guess that makes sense.
I feel bad, but I'm not able to
tell them apart otherwise.
I guess that makes sense.
Now that I think about it, this place
is really filling up with people living here.
Population
How many of us are there now?
A lot.
Hiraku!
I brought all the elves that were still
wandering the forest over here!
Oh...
N-now there are even more...
Are they all women?
Where are the men? I don't see any.
There weren't really any men who survived.
I see.
But that's okay.
We can just start making more now!
I hope that works out for you!
I decided not to ask them
how they planned to do it.
A few days later
Hey, what's going on?
Who knows? I'm just here
because I was asked to come.
He said to gather all the different
representatives here today...
I wonder if some sort of problem has arisen.
Hey, sorry for calling you all here like this.
There's something I want to talk about
with all of you today.
You see, I want to come up with
a name for this place.
This place here?
Yeah.
At first, it was just my little hut
and some crop fields,
but then more buildings started popping up
and more people started moving in.
It's like a village now, right?
That's why I want to come up with
a name for this village.
I like that idea!
A name for our town!
Can't we just name it after you
since you're the founder?
No...
Welcome
Come to Hiraku Village
Then it'd be something like Hiraku Village,
Gather at Machio Town
or maybe Machio Town.
I don't really like the sound of that.
In that case, how about we name it
after the forest we're in?
That sounds like a good idea.
By the way, what's this forest called?
The Forest of Death.
The Forest of Death
What, really? That's scary.
That makes this The Village of Death.
The Village of Death
Sounds like a ghost town.
It sounds like it'd have a poison swamp.
What is it?
This door?
You want me to open it?
This is The Great Tree Village.
Hello, everyone.
From now on, we've decided to
call this The Great Tree Village.
In celebration of this day,
we're going to have a party!
And no party would be complete without this!
The first batch of wine we made
here in The Great Tree Village!
Please enjoy yourselves, everyone!
Mayor!
Mayor! Mayor!
No, that's something we need to
decide together later.
What are you talking about?
You're the only one for the job.
She's right.
Everyone's already calling you mayor!
I-I see.
Fermentation
You're pretty drunk, huh?
What's wrong?
You're sitting all by yourself zoning out.
It's nothing.
I was just thinking about how I'm so happy
that this all feels like a dream.
This isn't a dream.
We're all going to keep living together,
enjoying our lives.
Yeah, you're right.
I'd like that.
Okay then!
Let's toast to The Great Tree Village.
Yeah.
Cheers.
No fair!
I'm going to toast, too!
You were awake?
C'mon!
Very well then.
How many years has it been?
Cheers!
It's been a while since I've had wine.
It tastes better than I remember.
Gimme another!
I guess I'll give it a shot,
as mayor.
Next Time
Episode 7
A Hospitable Heart
Next Time